So now, let's move on to the least upper bound operation. And once again, T and
现在，让我们来看看最小上界运算。再一次，T和
T prime will be any types except self-type. The least upper bound of self-type
T素数将是除自类型之外的任何类型。自体型的最小上界
with itself is just self-type, and I think that that's pret ty clear. The
它本身就是一种自我类型，我认为这一点非常清楚。这个
least upper bound of self-types of C and T will be the least upper bound of the class
C和T的自身类型的最小上界将是类的最小上界
C and T. And once again, this is because C is the largest type, that self-type could
再说一次，这是因为C是最大的类型，自我类型可以
be. And therefore, the largest type is guaranteed to cover both self-types of C.
就是这样。因此，最大的类型保证覆盖C的两个自身类型。
And T is going to be the least upper bound of C and T. And least of our bounds is the
T将是C和T的最小上界，我们的最小上界是
symmetric operations, so if I reverse these two arguments, the answer is the same.
对称运算，所以如果我颠倒这两个论点，答案是相同的。
And finally if self-type is not one of the arguments at least upper bound then
最后，如果Self-type不是参数之一，那么至少上界是这样的
we just do what we do before. The self-type, the least upper bound definition
我们只是做我们以前做过的事。自我类型，最小上界定义
excuse me, has not changed for class names for type names other than self-type.
对不起，对于除Self-type之外的其他类型名称的类名，没有更改。